{"response_code":0,"results":[{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"You can square root a negative number with an imaginary number &quot;i&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"The &#039;Squaring the Circle&#039; problem is solvable.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"The set of all algebraic numbers is countable.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"The binary number &quot;101001101&quot; is equivalent to the Decimal number &quot;334&quot;","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"A &#039;Millinillion&#039; is a real number.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"The Pythagorean theorem states that the square of the hypotenuse is equal to the product of the squares of the other two sides.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"Zero factorial is equal to zero. ","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"If you could fold a piece of paper in half 50 times, its&#039; thickness will be 3\/4th the distance from the Earth to the Sun.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"In Topology, the complement of an open set is a closed set.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]}
